export const data = [
  {
    id: "33",
    title: "Placement test",
    content: {
      list_question: [
        {
          question:
            "When you disagree with a group member’s idea, how do you typically respond?",
          type: 3,
          list_answer:
            "A) I ignore the disagreement and continue with my own ideas. | B) I express my disagreement strongly, trying to convince them of my viewpoint. | C) I listen to their perspective, discuss my own thoughts calmly, and work towards a compromise. | D) I avoid discussing it altogether to avoid conflict.",
          correct_answer: "1",
          group: "Emotional Intelligence (EQ)",
        },
        {
          question: "If a friend is upset, how do you usually react?",
          type: 3,
          list_answer:
            "A) I ignore their feelings and continue with my day. | B) I try to cheer them up by making jokes or distracting them. | C) I listen to them, acknowledge their feelings, and offer support if needed. | D) I tell them they need to get over it and move on.",
          correct_answer: "1",
          group: "Emotional Intelligence (EQ)",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Describe a time when you had to manage your emotions during a difficult situation. What did you learn from that experience?",
          type: 4,
          group: "Emotional Intelligence (EQ)",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which of the following comes next in this sequence? 2, 4, 8, 16, ___",
          type: 3,
          list_answer: "A) 18 | B) 24 | C) 32  | D) 64",
          correct_answer: "1",
          group: "Intelligence Quotient (IQ)",
        },
        {
          question:
            "A person needs to arrange 7 books on a shelf. If 2 specific books must always be next to each other, how many possible arrangements are there?",
          type: 3,
          list_answer: "A) 5! |  B) 6! | C) 7! | D) 6 × 5!",
          correct_answer: "1",
          group: "Intelligence Quotient (IQ)",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Consider this sequence of letters: A, B, D, F, H, __What is the next letter?",
          type: 3,
          list_answer: "A) I | B) J | C) K | D) L",
          correct_answer: "1",
          group: "Logic",
        },
        {
          question:
            "There are five people in a room: Adam, Ben, Carl, Dan, and Eric. Adam is taller than Ben, but shorter than Carl. Carl is shorter than Dan but taller than Eric. Who is the second tallest?",
          type: 3,
          list_answer: "A) Adam | B) Ben | C) Carl | D) Dan",
          correct_answer: "1",
          group: "Logic",
        },
        {
          question:
            "You are given a project with a tight deadline, but you also have a personal commitment. How do you approach this situation?",
          type: 3,
          list_answer:
            "A) I prioritize the personal commitment and delay the project. | B) I work on the project and ignore the personal commitment. | C) I evaluate both priorities, communicate with the relevant parties, and create a plan to balance both. | D) I ignore both and procrastinate until the last minute.",
          correct_answer: "1",
          group: "Critical Thinking",
        },
        {
          question:
            "You’re given two options: one is a job that pays well but offers little room for growth, and the other is a job with a lower salary but greater learning opportunities. What do you consider before making a decision?",
          type: 3,
          list_answer:
            "A) I choose the job with the higher salary. | B) I choose the job with better learning opportunities, because I value personal development. | C) I choose whichever job offers the quickest benefits. | D) I evaluate the long-term impact on my career and personal growth.",
          correct_answer: "1",
          group: "Critical Thinking",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is your career goal, and how have you planned for it?",
          type: 4,
          group: "Personal Motivation: Why Do You Want to Join This Program?",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Why do you want to join our career exploration program, and what do you hope to gain from this experience?",
          type: 4,
          group: "Personal Motivation: Why Do You Want to Join This Program?",
        },
      ],
      description: "<p>Quizz</p>",
      time_limit: "60",
    },
    category: "5",
    lang: "en",
  },
];
